[{"question": " hey! chandler, joey, and phoebe: hey!", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry i\u0092m late, did i miss anything?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " where were you?", "answer": " oh, on a date. yeah, i met this girl on the train going to a museum upstate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh, yeah! how did you meet her?", "answer": " oh, which museum?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  no, answer his.", "answer": " okay, it was just me and her at the back of the train, and i sat near the door, so she\u0092d have to pass by me if she wanted to switch cars. she was totally at my mercy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " were you so late because you were burring this woman?", "answer": " no, i\u0092m getting back down \u0091cause she lives in poughkeepsie. she seems really great, but she\u0092s like totally great, but she lives two and a half hours away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " how can she be great if she\u0092s from poughkeepsie?  that joke would\u0092ve killed in albany.", "answer": " done! i did it! heh, who\u0092s stupid now?  opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " hey, look at this!  they\u0092re lighting the big christmas tree tonight.", "answer": " umm, that paper\u0092s two weeks old.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " all right, who keeps leaving old newspapers in the trash?! i really wanted to take kathy to this, i can\u0092t believe i missed it.", "answer": " hey, y\u0092know, at least you have somebody to miss that stuff with! i hate being alone this time of year! next thing you know it\u0092ll be valentine\u0092s day, then my birthday, then bang!\u0097before you know it, they\u0092re lighting that damn tree again. ohh, i want somebody!  y\u0092know, i want a man!!  i mean, it doesn\u0092t even have to be a big relationship, y\u0092know, just like a fling would be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " really?! i didn\u0092t think girls ever just wanted a fling.", "answer": " well, believe me, it\u0092s been a long time since i\u0092ve been flung.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " well, i know what i\u0092m giving you for christmas.", "answer": " y\u0092know what? there\u0092s some nice guys at my office, do you want me to set you up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah! wait a minute, it\u0092s been a long time that i\u0092ve been single. how come you never offered this before?", "answer": " well, i have a girlfriend, i\u0092m-i\u0092m happy. so, i no longer feel the need to go out of my way to stop others from being happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " okay! no accountants. oh, and no one from like legal. i don\u0092t like guys with boring jobs.", "answer": " oh and ross was like what? a lion tamer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what\u0092s wrong mon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " ohh, everybody at the restaurant still hates me.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey, maybe they meant to write, \u0091quiet, bitch.\u0092", "answer": " hey, honey! what\u0092s the matter?  fine, i was just trying to be nice! whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " ohhh!", "answer": " i mean they\u0092re trying to do everything they can to make me quit, and if there were any other job, i would. but this is something i\u0092ve been waiting for my whole life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " well, wait a minute, you\u0092re the boss! why don\u0092t you just yell at them? or, fire them?", "answer": " i would love too, but i can\u0092t! i mean i just can\u0092t, you know that i\u0092m not good at confrontation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey, you know what you can do? i remember reading about this director, i think it was orson wells, who at the beginning of the movie would hire somebody, just so he could fire them in front of everybody. then they would all know, who\u0092s boss.", "answer": " hey, mon! i\u0092m not doing anything, why don\u0092t you fire me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " that\u0092s a good idea! wait, do you know how to waiter?", "answer": " good enough to get fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " all right, you\u0092re hired!", "answer": " hey! that must be why i got fired last week! does this orson wells guy direct burger king commercials?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i say, drew! are you seeing anybody right now?  og-ee-op, i\u0092m not asking for me, i\u0092m\u009a i mean\u009a no, i\u0092m-i\u0092m not gay, i\u0092m not asking you out. i\u0092m not-i\u0092m not-i\u0092m not gay!", "answer": " i didn\u0092t think you were gay. i do now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " see my friend-my friend, rachel, she wants to be set up.", "answer": " ahh, i just got out of a big relationship, i\u0092m not looking for any thing serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh, y\u0092know what, that might be okay even if it was just kind of a fling, that might be all right with rachel.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! is this, hot rachel, that you took to the christmas party, rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  oh, by the way, that is her full name.", "answer": " oh wow! i\u0092m free for her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh, wait a second! i didn\u0092t say i wasn\u0092t free!", "answer": " hey, chandler, why don\u0092t we talk this over at the ranger game tomorrow?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " hold on, y\u0092know i just got a box of cubans, maybe i bring them by your office around uh, five?", "answer": " oh well, that\u0092s uh, a little later than i uh, generally care to stay, but sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " maybe, before the game we could enjoy some eight year old some small batch basel hadens.", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t really know what that is, but let\u0092s!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hey! you guys, i\u0092m writing a holiday song for everyone. do you want to hear it? monica, rachel, and joey: yes!", "answer": "  happy chanukah, monica! may your christmas be snowy, joey! happy new year, chandler and ross. spin the draddle, rachel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " pheebs, that\u0092s great!", "answer": " oh, yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " but y\u0092know umm, rachel doesn\u0092t rhyme with draddle.", "answer": " i know but it\u0092s so hard! nothing rhymes with your stupid name!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " what are you talking about? lots of things rhyme with rachel. bagel. mail. jail. bail. able. may-pole.", "answer": " all good, thanks.  do you maybe have a nickname have like a nickname that\u0092s easier to rhyme?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " didn\u0092t your dad used to call you pumpkin?", "answer": " oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " pumpkin? yeah. but did he ever call you like, budolph?", "answer": "  hello, children!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  have i got the 50 guys for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " oh yeah, i just showed this a picture of you and guys were throwing themselves at me! they\u0092re buying me drinks! they\u0092re giving me stuff!  knicks tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " sure! where are the seats?", "answer": " wherever! i\u0092ve got like 20!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " so, will i like any of these guys?", "answer": " y\u0092know what, i\u0092m gonna uh, play the field just a little more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " chandler!", "answer": " guys are signing over their 401-k\u0092s to me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  you work with robots!!", "answer": "  yes.  okay, there\u0092s this one guy, patrick, i think you\u0092re gonna like him, he\u0092s really nice, he\u0092s funny, he\u0092s a swimmer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " ohh, i like swimmer\u0092s bodies!", "answer": " yes, and his father invented that magnetic strip on the back of credit cards.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " op, i like credit cards!", "answer": " see, i\u0092m not bad at this fixing up thing, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " well, so what does he do?", "answer": " oh, he works in the fine foods division.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " your company has a fine foods division?", "answer": " it\u0092s a big company, i don\u0092t\u0097if you\u0097i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " now, wait a second! you make food and robots?", "answer": " no! no, the robots just work for them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  all right, i\u0092m gonna go to work. does anybody have a problem with that?", "answer": " yeah, lady, i do! i got a problem with that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " you want a problem? i\u0092ll give you a problem!", "answer": " oh, what are you gonna do? you\u0092re gonna fire me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh, wow! i should get going. i-i got a date tonight.", "answer": " oh yeah! with who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " you know that girl i told you about who lives up in poughkeepsie?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " not her. yeah, this is someone else i meet, and i-i can\u0092t decide between the two of them. y\u0092know the one from poughkeepsie, even though she\u0092s a two hour train ride away, is really pretty, really smart, and-and a lot of fun. but this other girl, well, she lives right uptown. y\u0092know she\u0092s, well she\u0092s-she\u0092s just as pretty, i guess she\u0092s smart, she\u0092s not fun.", "answer": " if she\u0092s no fun, why do you want to date her at all?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " well, i-i want to give her another chance, y\u0092know? she lives so close. and, at the end of the date, the other time, she-she said something that was\u0097if she was kidding was very funny. on the other hand, if she wasn\u0092t kidding, she\u0092s not fun, she\u0092s stupid, and kind of a racist.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hey! ooh, how was your first day working at the restaurant?", "answer": "  damn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " they baked it. i can\u0092t take this anymore. i\u0092m gonna call a meeting tonight, i\u0092m gonna fire you tonight.", "answer": " you got it! oh-oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " what are you doing?!", "answer": " it\u0092s still a tiny bit on fire there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  chandler!! you have the best taste in men!", "answer": " well, like father, like son.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " patrick and i had such a great time last night! i mean i think this could maybe turn into something serious.", "answer": " really?! i-i thought you weren\u0092t looking for something serious? i thought you were looking for some kind of a fling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " well, y'know, possibly.  you didn\u0092t tell him that, though? right?", "answer": " ummmmmmmm, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you told this guy that i was looking for a fling?! you don\u0092t tell the guy that!", "answer": " why not?! i\u0092d be thrilled if i heard that some hot girl was just looking to get\u0097oh i see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " hey, joey, could you pass the cheese?", "answer": " yeah. listen uh, i\u0092d prefer it if you didn\u0092t call me joey. since i don\u0092t know anyone here, i thought it\u0092d be cool to try out a cool work nickname.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  there\u0092s like-there\u0092s like 300 bucks in this one!", "answer": " yeah, people get pretty generous around the holidays. and it never hurts to wear tight trousers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " okay. could the waiters gather around to hear tonight\u0092s specials? okay, first there is a chilean sea bass prepared with a mango relish on a bag\u0097why is nobody writing these down?", "answer": " because we can remember them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " because your all gonna make up fake specials and make me cook them like you did the other night?", "answer": " well, sure, that too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " okay, forget the specials for a minute. umm, all right here\u0092s the thing, for the last two weeks i have umm,  tried really hard to create a positive atmosphere\u009a", "answer": " can\u0092t hear you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  a positive atmosphere! but i-i-i have had it up to here.  from now on, it is gonna be my way, or the highway! all right? does anybody have a problem with that?!!  hey new guy! i said, does anybody have a problem with that?!", "answer": " no ma\u0092am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " what the hell happened?!", "answer": " i am so-so-so sorry. i was gonna do it! really! but i was standing there with 327 dollars in one hand and 238 dollars in the other hand, and i was thinking, \"wow! it\u0092s been a long time since i had\u009a  327 + 238 dollars!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " joey, we had a deal. that-that\u0092s why you\u0092re here! i\u0092ve got to fire you!", "answer": " and i gotta pay rent! look, how-how about this? you don\u0092t fire me, instead i stay here, i gain their trust, and they\u0092ll start listening to all the nice things i\u0092ve been saying about you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " what kinda things have you been saying?", "answer": " well nothing yet, they really hate you and i want to fit in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  happy, happy chanukah, chandler and monica. very merry\u009a", "answer": "  oh, y\u0092know, y\u0092know what pheebs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i\u0092m not jewish, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " bad dream?", "answer": " i wasn\u0092t sleeping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " oh yeah, then uh, what was phoebe\u0092s song about?", "answer": " the one with the cat. i gotta go, i\u0092ve got another date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " so, did you pick one yet?", "answer": " no, it turns out that the one from uptown was making a joke. but it was a different joke than i thought\u0097it wasn\u0092t that funny. so i\u0092m still torn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well look, you don\u0092t really like the one from uptown and you\u0092re too exhausted from dating the one up in poughkeepsie, so i say you just end them both. okay? you take a train up to poughkeepsie and break up with her, and on your way back you break up with uptown. and then by the time you get home tonight, you\u0092re done!", "answer": " y\u0092know, you\u0092re right. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " umm, well i had a similar problem when i lived in prague.", "answer": " prague?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " chandler! patrick just uh, ended things with me. did you or did you not tell him that i was looking for a serious relationship?", "answer": " i did! i absolutely did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " you idiot!!", "answer": " i\u0092m sure you\u0092re right, but why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " you don\u0092t tell a guy that you\u0092re looking for a serious relationship! you don\u0092t tell the guy that! now you scared him away!", "answer": " oh, man. i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m so-so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " y\u0092know, you should never be allowed to talk to people!", "answer": " i know! i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! you graduated magma ku laude, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " oh, it doesn\u0092t matter.  hey, y\u0092know what, i\u0092ve got two tickets to tonight\u0092s rangers game, you wanna come with me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " cute guys in little shorts? sure.", "answer": " well, actually it\u0092s a hockey team, so it\u0092s angry canadians with no teeth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " have you ever been with a woman?", "answer": " what?! chandler, what is the matter with you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i need more swordfish.  can you get me some more swordfish?", "answer": " i don\u0092t speak english.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " you did a minute ago!", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t know what to tell ya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " you found that handle, did ya?", "answer": " that\u0092s not funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " well that\u0092s not true.", "answer": "  i\u0092m a good person. and i\u0092m a good chef, and i don\u0092t deserve to have marinara sauce all over me! y\u0092know what, if you want me to quit this bad, then all you have to do is\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "  hey! chef geller! y\u0092know that little speech you made the other day? well i got a problem with it!", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " you bet i do! i just ah, wasn\u0092t listening then, that\u0092s all.", "answer": " well if you want a problem? i\u0092ll give you a problem!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what are you gonna do? you\u0092re gonna fire me?", "answer": " you bet your ass i\u0092m gonna fire you! get out of my kitchen! get out!!  all right! anybody else got a problem? how \u0091bout you chuckles? you think this is funny now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " how about if i dance around all covered in sauce? huh? you think it\u0092s funny now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s really good.", "answer": " good! now, take those salads to table 4,  and you! get the swordfish!  and you! get a haircut!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " last stop, montreal. this stop is montreal.", "answer": "  what?  woman on train: i made a bet with myself that you have beautiful eyes. now that i see them, i win.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what? woman on train: we\u0092re at my stop. but would you like to have coffee?", "answer": "  are we really in montreal?! woman on train: yes we are. so, coffee?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " well i guess i should\u0092ve thought about my wife and kids before i talked back to chef geller!", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yep! looks like it\u0092s gonna be a leeeeean christmas at the dragon house this year.", "answer": " enough!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  \"went to the store, sat on santa's lap.", "answer": "asked him to bring my friends all kind of crap.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "said all you need is to write them a song.", "answer": "they haven't heard it, so don't try and sing along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "no, don't sing along.", "answer": "monica, moncia, have a happy chanukah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "saw santa clause, he said hello to ross.", "answer": "and plese tell joey, christmas will be snowy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}]